（忆往昔）
你骗了我 又一次
You lied to me again.
所以你就决定骗我同意
You decide to trick me into being possessed.
让一个疯子天使附身吗 看看都发生了什么
By some psycho angel. And now.
Kevin的死都怪我
Kevin's blood is on my hands.
我会找到Gadreel
But I'll find Gadreel.
然后亲手结果了那个混蛋 但我要一个人去
And I'll end that son of a bitch.But I'll do it alone.
你这是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean.
Sam 跟我有关的人
Sam, people get close to me.
都被杀害了 有的情况更糟
They gey killed or worse.
走吧
Just go.
我不会拦着你的
I'm not gonna stop you.
这他妈是Cain之印
It's the bloody Mark of Cain.
标记和初刃是相辅相成的
The mark and the Blade work together.
如果这真的是你想要的结果
I can give you the mark, Dean.
我可以把标记传给你 Dean
If it's what you truly want.
标记是可以转移给其他人的
The mark can be transferred.
我打给了一个朋友 Garth
I called a friend of ours, Garth.
他跟我们是同行 做事情很独特
He does what we do, in his own way.
别再犯傻了
Stop being an idjit.
你知道这样做的后果是什么
Now you know what's coming next, right.
天呐 太好吃了
Man, this is good.
大丹麦狗马默杜克 你真是疯了
Oh, Marmaduke, you're crazy.
Garth呢
And where's Garth.
去查案子了 也可能去看牙医了
On a case…or the dentist.
我 我不知道 我很久没跟他联系过了
I…I don't know, I haven't heard from him.
Garth他人还是没有消息吗
Garth still MIA.
（格兰茨堡 威斯康辛州）
嘿
Hey.
（格兰茨堡纪念医院）
下午好
Good afternoon.
我在找人
I'm looking for a John Doe.
大概是几天前住的院
That was admitted here a few days ago.
他很
He is a.
瘦 长得跟Ichabod Crane似的
Skinny, Ichabod Crane, looking kind of guy.
我知道你说的是谁了 113号房 探员先生
I know just who you mean.Room 113, agent.
好的 谢谢
All right, thanks.
这两天找他的人还挺多
Sure is a popular fella.
我监听了警察内线 发现Garth就是那个无名氏
Saw Garth's John Doe on the police wire.
你呢
You.
一样
Yeah.
你从哪儿赶过来的
Where you coming from.
新墨西哥
New Mexico.
长途跋涉啊
Well, that's haul.
考虑到我一个人就能处理好这事儿
Especially considering that I got this.
如果你想走人的话
Pretty much covered, so if you wanna.
你跟他谈过了吗
You spoken to him yet.
还没有
No.
他注射了止痛剂
Assload of painkillers.
我来的时候他就睡着
He's been out since I got here.
他犯了什么事儿
What's he being charged with.
杀了一头牛
Killing a cow.
为什么
Why.
我正打算看看能问出什么来
I was about to see if I could find out.
把门锁上
Lock the door.
嘿
Whoa, hey.
那是什么 肾上腺素
What is that?Adrenaline.
没错
Yes, sir.
你是想把他叫醒 还是想杀了他
Are you trying to jump-start him or kill him.
我只想要一个答案
I want some answers.
他背弃了Kevin
He walked out on Kevin.
背弃了我们
He walked out on us.
除非你有更好的办法
So if you got a better idea.
Dean
Dean.
Sam
Sam.
这是哪里 医院吗
What is this?A hospital.
等等
Wait.
难道我上天堂了
Am I in heaven.
好了 别紧张 Garth
All right, take it easy, Garth.
这儿是威斯康辛
You're in Wisconsin.
你被一辆车撞了
You're hit by a car.
你还记得什么吗
Do you remember anything.
我 呃 很模糊
I-uh…vaguely.
手铐是怎么回事儿
What's with the hardware.
我还想问你呢
You tell us.
既然你在这里 为什么不说说你擅离职守的
While you're at it.Why don't you give us some lowdown.
6个月里 跑去哪里快活了
On why you went AWOL for the past six months.
我们是知道了你杀了一头牛之后才找到你的
Only way we tracked you down is that you offed a cow.
杀了什么东西
Offed a what.
我 我当时在查一个案子
I…I was on a hunt.
什么案子
Hunt for what.
我 哦不 我马上回来
I…oh no, I'll get back.
哦 我的妈
Oh, god.
真庆幸我没有给他注射肾上腺素
Good thing I didn't give him the adrenaline.
Gadreel的事儿有什么进展吗
Anything on Gadreel.
事实上 还真有
Actually, yeah.
我们发现他在逃跑之前
Turns out that he left some grace in me.
在我体内留下了一部分荣光
Before he bolted.
你明白这听起来情况很不妙 对吧
You know how wrong that sounds, right.
不用担心 Cass都治疗得很好
Wouldn't worry about it.Cass took care of it.
怎么了
What.
没什么 只是我刚走了俩星期
Nothing, I'm gone for two weeks.
感觉你好像跟少年妈妈一样糟糕
And you're like an episode of Teen Mom.
呼吸 Garth 吐完就好了
Just breathe, Garth, work it out.
你胳膊那儿怎么回事
What happened to your arm.
这个啊
Well, it's a.
是Cain送的小礼物
A gift from Cain.
你是说 摔跤选手那个吗
Like…the wrestler.
我倒希望是
I wish.
那样就帅多了
That'd be awesome.
不是 一个旧约里的老头子而已
No.The Old Testament dude.
我们俩看对了眼 然后他就把他的烙印传给我了
He got biblical on me and gave me his mark.
你到底什么意思 为什么会发生这种事情
What does this even mean.How did that happen.
Crowley和我找到了他 他把烙印传给我
Crowley and I found him and he gave me this.
然后我就能永远解决掉Abaddon
So that I can 86 Abaddon once and for all.
你跟Crowley一起查案子了
You worked a job with Crowley.
就是你认识的那个
The devil you know.
Garth
Garth.
怎么了
What.
他个小混蛋
Son of a bitch.
Garth怎么能从我们眼皮子底下溜掉
How would Garth run from us.
他过去6个月为什么没有一点儿音讯
Why haven't we hear from him for the last six months.
你测试过他了吗
Did you test him.
他正昏迷着 我当然没有
He was unconscious, no.I.
他偷了辆车
He steal a car.
而且还是光着身子偷的
Did he steal a car naked.
我去看看这些摄像头拍到了什么
See what I could find on those cameras.
你可以去跟那个叫Brown的农场主谈谈
Why don't you go talk to farmer Brown.
- 问问那头牛的事儿 - 好吧
- See about that cow - Yeah.
上周 死的是几只鸡
Last week, it was a couple of chickens.
上上周 是羊
Goat, the week before that.
有人看见那男孩子从我的谷仓里跑出来
So when I saw that boy tearing out of my barn.
那我肯定得先抄家伙上啊
Hell yeah I was gonna ask questions later.
那些动物都是死于相同的手法吗
Now, the animals were they all killed in the same manner.
更像是献祭
More like sacrificed.
为什么这么说
What do you mean by that.
他们的内脏都被挖走了
Their organs was ripped clean out.
只有内脏
Only the organs.
如果这不是什么恶魔崇拜之类的事情
If this wasn't some kind of devil-worship thing.
我就不清楚了
I don't know what.
谢谢
Well, thanks.
怎么
Yeah.
所以那头牛不仅仅是被杀死了
So the cow wasn't just killed.
还被挖走了内脏
It was eviscerated.
Garth为什么在那儿
Why was Garth there.
他说他在查案子 对吧
He said he was on a hunt, right.
说不定他就是在追杀牛的罪魁祸首
Maybe he's hunting whatever killed it.
那他看见咱俩为什么要跑
Why would he run.
这事儿绝对不简单
This whole thing's starting to stink.
你肯定能看出来
You know that, right.
是啊
Yeah.
你呢 有什么发现吗
What about you, any luck.
什么都没有
Nada.
监视器拍摄的角度不对
Cameras were pointing in the wrong direction.
开玩笑吧
You kidding.
我倒希望是
Wish I was.
- 那么 - 既然Garth是个猎人
- So - So, Garth's a hunter.
他不想被人找到的时候 谁都找不到他
If he wants to stay gone, he's gone.
我们走进了死胡同
We got nothing.
我还能怎么说呢 Sammy
Well, what can I say, Sammy.
这事儿咱们管不了 别忘了给我寄明信片
We lost this one.Send me a postcard.
哇 车子形状 型号
Wow, make, model.
还有车牌号都照到了
License plate.
真的吗 Dean
Really, Dean.
我跟你说过我们不能再在一起查案子了
I told you we can't hunt together.
这是为了你好
It's for your own good.
我知道
I hear you.
只要我弄清楚Garth到底在搞什么鬼
And after we find Garth and get to the bottom of this.
我就走人
I'm gone.
但在此之前 别再跟我耍小花招了
But until then, no more games.
那车的主人是个叫Bess Meyers的女孩
Ride belongs to a girl named Bess Meyers.
她家就在旁边的镇子里
She lives in the next town over.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
我能解释
I can explain.
一切都很好 只是有点儿小误会
Everything's cool.Just a simple misunderstanding.
你在跟谁说话
Who you talking to.
什么
What.
那个女孩吗
The girl.
什么女孩
What what girl.
现在又怎么了
What, now.
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
你们俩 大家都冷静一下
Guys, everyone needs to take a chill pill.
然后把枪放下
And put their guns down.
什么人都没有吧
You see.
咱们现在表现得成熟一点
Let's all be grown-ups here.
来场大人之间的谈话吧
And have an adult conversation.
不
No.
Sam
Sam.
Sam 求你了 别伤害她
Sam, please, don't hurt her.
你在干什么
What are you doing.
她是个狼人
She's werewolf.
我也是
So am I.
没事的 宝贝
It's okay, baby.
这样按住你的伤口
Hold it like that.
他们在这儿干什么 Garth
What are they doing here, Garth.
他们是朋友 我保证
They're friends, I promise.
可他们是猎人
They're hunters.
好吧 大家初次见面 产生了不小的误会
All right, we've all gotten off on the wrong foot here.
咱们再来重新认识一下
So let's do things right.
伙计们 这是Bess
Boys, this is Bess.
我的爱人
My beloved.
Bess 这是Dean
And Bess, that's Dean.
虽然他现在火气大到能对着一屋子空气打架
Now, he could start a fight in an empty house.
但是在内心深处
But deep down inside.
他就是个大号泰迪熊
He's just a big old Teddy bear.
这边这位是Sam
And Sam here.
Sam有的时候可能会变得危险
Sam can be a bit insecure at times.
但那都是有原因的
But for good reason.
上帝保佑他
Bless his heart.
说得真好听
That's sweet.
狼人
Werewolf.
好了 伙计们 听着
All right, guys, look.
6个月以前
About 6 months ago.
我在缅因州 波特兰市外
I was outside Portland, Maine.
追捕一只狼人
Hunting this big bad wolf.
我把它干掉了 但是
I took him down, but.
他咬了我
He bit me in the process.
你怎么就没想着给我们打个电话
And you didn't call one of us.
然后告诉你们什么
And tell you what.
告诉你们我搞砸了吗
That I messed up.
不 我知道这种事情的后果
No, I knew the deal.
不可能有解药 所以我只能接受
There's no cure, so I accepted my fate.
吃了我最喜欢的芙蓉蛋
Ate my favourite dish of egg fu yung.
看了全宇宙最棒的电影洛奇3 然后
Watched the world's greatest movie Rocky III.And then.
然后 我做好了上路的准备
Was ready to eat a bullet.
就在那时 Bess找到了我
When Bess here found me.
她怎么找到你的
And how'd she do that.
我闻到了他 不然呢
Smelled him.How else.
是啊
Yeah.
她说服我把枪从嘴里拿出来
She talked the gun out of my mouth.
然后就想人们说的那样 过去的就过去了
And as they say, the rest is history.
我们已经结婚4个月了
We've been married for 4 months now.
你结婚了
You're married.
跟一只狼人
To a werewolf.
是的
Yes.
我的族人接受他作为其中一员
And my pack has taken him in as one of our own.
伙计们 这跟你们想的不一样
Guys, it's not what you think.
我们从不伤害人类
We don't hurt people.
当然不 你们只对着牛才会热血喷张
No, you just go all Wolverine on cattle.
是啊
Yeah.
至少他没有吃人类的心脏
At least he's not eating human hearts.
你们知道对于一个像Garth一样被咬的狼人
Do you have any idea how hard it is for a bitten.
控制住自己的本能是多么困难吗
To control his instincts like Garth does.
他现在做的很好
How well he's doing.
谢谢 亲爱的
Thank you baby.
这是事实 亲爱的
Well, it's the truth, honey bunny.
等等 被咬吗
Wait, a…a bitten.
你们都是被咬的吗
You're all bitten.
不完全是
Not at all.
你也可以是天生狼人 像我
You're either born to it, like I was.
或者是被咬而变成狼人 像Garth
Or you're bitten like Garth.
等等
Hold on.
你是说你一出生就是狼人吗
You said you're-you're born a werewolf.
我是第二代
Second generation.
Garth 我们可以和你谈谈吗 单独的
Garth, can we talk to you for a sec, alone.
亲爱的 你去找找药膏擦擦手臂吧
Honey, why don't you to find some ointment for that arm.
好吗
Okay.
究竟怎么回事
What the hell.
我知道你们想要先动手
Look, I know you guys want to shoot first.
再问问题 但是我已经四处查看过了
And ask questions later, but I checked everything out.
这里没有问题
This pack is clean.
一切都很干净
Everything's Kosher.
没错 除了你妻子袭击我那一部分
Right, minus the part where your wife attacked me.
是啊 因为你俩闯进来
Yeah, because you two came busting in here.
好像房子着火了一样
Like a house on fire.
拿着枪乱指 这下巴 这发型
Guns waving, the jawlines and the hair.
实在是太吓人了
It's very intimidating.
谁能预料到啊
What'd you expect.
Dean 没人想要惹麻烦
Dean, no one wants any trouble.
你可以相信我
You got my word on that.
不 我已经不相信你了
Oh, no.That ship has sailed.
我们需要更多的线索 不止是你的话
We're gonna need a hell of a lot more than your word.
行 行 告诉你
Okay, Okay.Tell you what.
你想要证明
You want proof.
来跟我们一起祈祷吧
Come pray with us.
你还在吗
You there.
嗯 刚停好车
Yeah, just pulled up.
暂时还是一知半解
Nothing too sketchy yet.
这是好事 对吗
That's a good thing, right.
别希望太大
Not betting on it.
还是我们都如此悲观了
Or are we just that jaded.
我是说 或许Garth是对的
I mean, maybe Garth's right.
你是不是瞎了眼啊
Well, ain't you a glass half full.
警察那里有线索吗
Any luck with the cops.
警长等下就会回来
Sheriff should be rolling up any second.
小心点
Be careful.
好
Yeah.
我们在第二节要唱得重一些
We need to come in strong on the second verse.
再来一遍
Let's try it again.
Garth 从这里开始弹
Garth, play it from here.
然后
And.
你一定是Dean
You must be Dean.
我是Joy Garth的岳母
I'm Joy, Garth's mother-in-law.
继岳母才对
Uh, stepmother-in-law.
虽然我觉得听起来很傻
Which I always thought sounded so silly.
请进
Please, come in.
我们快结束了
We're just finishing up.
你直接跟Garth说我来了吧
Why don't you just tell Garth I'm here.
Dean 相信我
Dean, you have my word.
在我这里 你是安全的
You're safe under my roof.
同样我也想问同一个问题
I only ask the same in return.
毕竟
After all.
我并不是那个带着银子弹的人
I'm not the one carrying silver.
谢谢 Garth
Thank you brother Garth.
完美的伴奏 一如既往
Wonderful accompaniment, as usual.
我们在教堂里再见吧
And I'll see the rest of you in the pews.
九点整
9 am, sharp.
不能迟到哦 Amelia
No stragglers, sister Amelia.
嗨
Oh, hi.
我要跟你说什么呢 一切都正常 对吗
So, what'd I tell you, it's all good, right.
这些人都是狼人吗
Everyone here's a wolf.
是啊
Yeah.
这样吗 那就不怎么好了
Yeah, not all good.
别闹别扭了 Dean
Oh, come on, Dean.
你一定要来见见大家伙儿
You just gonna meet them.
那是Russ和Joba
That's Russ and Joba.
Bess在Joy家的表兄弟
Bess' first cousins on sister Joy's side.
那位是Jim神父 Bess的爸爸
That's reverend Jim, Bess' dad.
同时也是狼群的首领 他是个好人
Leader of the pack and a good man.
你就是Dean对吧
Dean, isn't it.
欢迎
Welcome.
我是Jim Meyers 但大家一般都叫我
Jim Meyers, folks usually call me.
Jim神父 我听说了
Reverend Jim, yeah, I got it.
我太冒失了
My bad.
Dean他有严重的洁癖
Dean's got this crazy fear of germs.
我理解你的顾虑 Dean
I understand your apprehension, Dean.
猎人和我们一族
Hunters and our kind.
从来就没有什么好结果
Don't have the best history together.
但我想你会发现
But I think you'll find.
其实我们并没有什么区别
We're not much different from you.
哦 教友 对于这点我非常怀疑
Oh, sister, I highly doubt it.
不如留下来跟我们一起吃个饭吧
Why don't we break bread.
你就会知道了
And see.
我为什么要答应你
Why would I do that.
Dean
Dean.
怎么
What.
好了 大家开动吧
Now, everybody eat up.
别忘了留点儿肚子吃派
Make sure you leave room for pie.
Joy做的派
Sister Joy's pies are famous.
可是威斯康辛一绝
Throughout the badger state.
Dean最爱吃派了
Dean loves pie.
你们不说点儿餐前祷告语什么的吗
Don't you guys say some sort of a grace or something.
相对于宗教 我们更信仰精神的力量
We're more spiritual than we are religious.
我们的信仰 和美国印第安人差不多
We believe, much like the American Indians did.
天人合一
That nature and man are one.
是啊 他们确实干得不错
Yeah, really worked out well for them.
为什么你们这群狼人
So why are a bunch of werewolves wearing.
都把银子弹戴在脖子上
Silver bullets around their necks.
Dean 不好意思 我们不用W开头的那个词
Sorry, Dean, but we don't use the W word around here.
我们更倾向于于变狼患者这个词
We prefer the term lycanthrope.
我们
We.
他有权表达自己的观点 Garth
He is entitled to his opinion, Garth.
我们种族的许多人认为自己是坚不可摧的
Many of our kind see themselves as indestructible.
这颗子弹能够时常提醒我们
This is a constant reminder of.
要好好珍惜我们现在的生活
How precious our lives truly are.
我懂 但是那是银制的 不会烧伤自己吗
Yeah, but it's silver, I mean, doesn't it burn.
是啊 有一点
Yeah, it does a bit.
但是这才是关键
But that's kind of the point.
让我们记住自己的弱点
It reminds us of our fragility.
我女儿 Bess 天生就是狼人
My daughter, Bess, was born a lycanthrope.
那曾是我最骄傲的一段日子
It's one of the proudest days of my life.
但当猎人杀死了我妻子
Which soon turned tragic.
这一切瞬间成了悲剧
When a hunter killed my wife.
当我说我要那个人付出代价的时候
Believe me when I tell you.
相信我 我是认真的
I wanted to make someone pay.
后来我看到了Bess
Then I looked at Bess.
才明白
And I realized the road to revenge.
复仇之路是如此黑暗和孤独
Is a dark and lonely one.
你会永远摆脱不了的
Which you never get off.
然后就在你心里留下烙印
And that hole in the pit of you stomach.
你永远都没法填补它
You never fill it, ever.
我明白了
Hey, no, I get it.
所以我选择向前看 忘记过往
So I chose to look forward, not backwards.
就在我这样做了之后
And the minute I did that.
上帝让这个美丽热情的
The powers that be brought this beautiful.
女人走进了我的生活
Compassionate, amazing woman into my life.
她对待Bess如同自己亲生女儿般
And she helped me raise a little babygirl.
养育她长大
As if Bess were her own.
我不能霸占所有功劳
I can't take all the credit.
爸爸也有帮忙
Daddy had a hand in it, too.
他发现了你的潜能
He saw your potential.
爸爸
Daddy.
我的父亲 愿他安息
My father, bless his soul.
他以前是我们教堂的教士
Was the previous reverend of our church.
是我们家族第三代
The third generation in our family to serve.
所以你们是第四代
So you are the forth-generation werewolf.
是的
Yes.
教士Jim
Look, the good reverend Jim.
和他的家人
And his family are all a little.
都有点老派和落伍
New-agey and hippie-dippie like.
但是他们很真诚友善
But they are clean as whistle.
是我们小区的支柱
And pillars of our community.
为什么FBI会对他们感兴趣
Why is the FBI even interested in them.
我只是跟踪线索罢了 警长
I just go where they send me, Sheriff.
说实话 我更感兴趣的是
Truth be told, I'm more interested in.
谋杀或者X档案之类的
Murders and X-files-y stuff.
这附近有什么不寻常吗
Anything of that variety around here.
没有了 先生 我们这是个小镇
No sir, we are just a small town.
没有什么犯罪可言
Not much crime to any to speak of.
对不起 真希望我能帮上忙
I'm sorry, agent, I wish I could be more help.
没关系
That's all right.
你想起什么其他的 就给我打电话
But if you do think of something, give me a call.
一定
Will do.
还没吃饱
Still hungry.
呃 我只是 看看你们有没有啤酒
Yeah, I was just…seeing if you had any beer.
一旦你明白这里其实一切都很好
The sooner you realize that all is good here.
你就可以离开了
The sooner you can go.
你俩没有咬咬玩具什么的
Don't you two have a chew toy.
可以玩的吗
Or something to go play with.
嘿 伙计们
Hey guys.
介意我单独和Dean说两句吗
Mind if I grap a second with Dean here.
你为什么要这么为难我们
Why are you being so hard on everyone.
因为这里的一切绝不可能
Because there is no way that all of this.
如表面这么简单的
Is what it looks like.
不可能
No way.
为什么
Why not.
别这样 老兄 我知道你一定是喝醉了
Come on man, I know you drank the kool-aid, okay.
但是 拜托
But come on.
朋友
Look, amigo.
我知道这一切都很疯狂 但是
I know this is all looks nuts, but.
我终于找到了
I found it.
爱和家庭
Love and a family.
谁会去在意那些是从何而来
Who cares where that comes from.
我在意
I do.
我懂的
I get it.
我刚来这里的时候
When I first got here.
我也不能够释怀
I couldn't let go either.
我一直等待着更坏的情况发生
I kept waiting for the other shoe to drop.
但是那并没有
But when it didn't.
于是我学着接受真相
I had to accept the truth.
让我告诉你另一个真相
I got another truth for you.
在你擅离职守期间 我们完全找不到你
We were all left in the dark when you went AWOL.
我们也不知道你是死了还是遭遇更惨
I didn't know whether you were dead or worse.
你应该跟我们联系 发个信息
You should've reached out and sent someone a message.
说什么 Dean
And said what, Dean.
说我是个狼人吗
That I was a werewolf.
我无法启齿
I was embarrassed.
我以为我躲得远远的 对大家都好
I thought it's best for everyone if I just stayed away.
但并不意味着
But that doesn't mean that.
我不想念你和Sam
I didn't think about and miss you and Sam.
还有Kevin
Kevin.
Kevin死了
Kevin's gone.
什么
What.
他永远离开了
Gone for good.
怎么回事
What happened.
当他需要我的时候 我没有在他身边 就这样
When he needed me, I wasn't there.That's what.
好吧 Dean，他们给了你午饭和派
Okay, Dean, they gave you lunch and pie.
那为什么我们还在这
Why are we still here.
你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
Garth很好
Yeah, Garth's good.
你想要先离开的话 我完全同意
You want to hit the road, it's square by me.
我只是说 这不是我们第一次遇到的
Look, I'm just saying, this wouldn't be the first time.
友善的怪物
We came across a friendly monster.
或是友善的怪物家族
Or a family of friendly monsters.
不管是什么都好
Whatever this is.
我是Perry探员
Agent Perry.
警长 有什么事
Sheriff, how can I help you.
真的吗
Really.
没问题
Okay.
你想要奇怪的发现 探员
Well, you wanted weird, agent.
你告诉我是什么杀了这头鹿
You tell me what torn up that deer.
这一片已经没什么动物经过了
Nothing that runs in these this parts.
血液是新鲜的
It's fresh blood.
是的
Yes, it is.
还有温度
Still warm.
这头鹿是我们接到电话以后才被杀的
It means it died after we got the call.
你们就不能承认这里是一切正常 然后离开吗
Couldn't just accept all was good and move on, could you.
你们根本不知道自己卷进了什么里面
You have no idea what you've walked into, do you.
无所谓了 你们不会活着离开这里了
No matter, you won't be walking out of here.
看这个
Hey, look at this.
我之前见过这个
I've seen that before.
这是好人教士家
Yeah, that is favourite accessary.
最喜欢的饰品
Of good reverend and his floke.
诸神的黄昏
Ragnarok.
就是Thor Loki还有Odin之类的 对吗
It's a Thor, Loki and Odin stuff, right.
是 是古老的北欧神话了
Yeah, it's Norse mythology's end of days.
为什么会刻在子弹上面
Why is it etched onto a bullet.
谁在乎 我们需要的答案找到了
Who cares, we got all the answers we need.
我不清楚 Dean 我想我们还需要更多线索
I don't know, Dean, I think we need more.
什么 这个警长
Oh, what?Sheriff Andy Taylor here.
还不够线索吗
Wasn't good enough for you.
足够杀死Garth吗
Enough to kill Garth.
别这样 老兄 我们要好好解决这件事
Come on man, let's do this right.
好吧 把这里清理干净
Well, fine.Clean these up.
把Garth抓起来锁好
Grab Garth and lock him up.
直到我们找到真相
Untill we figure out what's what.
我去看看那个教堂
I'm gonna go check out that church.
Garth
Garth.
不是吧
Seriously.
（诸神的黄昏）
（斯堪的纳维亚神话传说 世界末日）
你找到那对爱情鸟了吗
Did you find the lovebirds.
没
No.
这里乱七八糟
The place is a wreck.
没看到Garth 也没看到Bess
No Garth, no Bess.
他们被抓走了吗
What, they were taken.
这下他妈的好极了
It's fan-friggin'-tastic.
你查到什么了吗
Tell me you got something.
有一个叫诸神的黄昏 世界末日的东西
There's a Ragnarok, end of the days, crap.
故事从一个叫做Fenris的巨狼开始
Start the story with a wolf named Fenris.
他在世界末日之前杀了Odin
Who kills the God Odin before the world ends.
好的 知道这个有什么用
Okay, and that helps us how.
有些邪教组织
There are cults that.
将Fenris视作巨狼之神来崇拜他
Consider Fenris a wolf deity and worship him.
并将自己称作Fenris之腹
They call themselves the Maw of Fenris.
信仰狼人的邪教
A cult to werewolves.
他们想怎样
What do they want.
诸神的黄昏不只是个圣经故事而已
Well, Ragnarok is not just a Bible story, these nutjobs.
它是个蓄谋已久的计划
It's an action plan.
灭绝人类
Human extinction.
纯粹彻底的狼人统治
Total and complete werewolf domination.
所以 这里就是一切开始的地方吗
And, what, this is the ground zero for the movement.
该死的威斯康辛州
Freakin' Wisconsin, man.
Jim神父该下台了
Now it's the time for reverend Jim to go down.
是啊
Yeah.
你需要帮忙吗
Need any help.
不 不 我搞的定
No no, I got it.
你去找到Garth就行
You just you find Garth.
好的
All right.
别躲着了 Dean 我听得到你的心跳
It's no use, Dean.I can hear your heartbeat.
你这样做有无数次了
You must have done this countless times.
但是你还是会紧张
Yet you still get nervous.
没有恐惧的话 怎么能叫做人类
Nothing wrong with a little fear.It's what makes us human.
恐惧并不是人类的专利
Fear is not a purely human instinct.
怪物们也会感到恐惧
Even monsters know fear.
我是来准备我的布道的
I came to work on my sermon.
你先给我讲讲Fenris之腹是怎么回事吧
Why don't you start by preaching to me about the Maw of Fenris.
对 是的
Yeah, that's right.
我已经知道你和你族群的计划了
I know all about you and your pack's little plan.
我向你保证 我们没有什么计划
I assure you, we are planning nothing.
是吗 那为什么我在你的经书里读到了这些
No?Then why did I read about it in your good book.
因为几十年前
Because generations ago.
仇恨和错误的愤懑是我们信仰的一部分
That hate and misplaced anger was part of our beliefs.
但是自从我接手这个之后
But ever since I took over here.
我把这部分从我们教会中彻底根除了
I have eradicated it from our congregation.
很明显他们中间有些人没听到你的教导
Apparently some of them didn't get the word.
比如那个
Like the good sheriff.
想杀死我和我弟弟的好人警长
Who just tried to off me and my brother.
Pat警长吗
Sheriff Pat.
让我看看你的子弹
Let me see your bullet.
在哪里
Where is it.
什么在哪里
Where is what.
诸神的黄昏
Ragnarok.
什么
What.
警长的子弹里就嵌着这个
It was etched into the sheriff's bullet.
不可能 那一族的人已经都死光了
That's impossible.The Maw is dead.
那你怎么解释Garth还有你女儿的失踪
Tell that to Garth and your daughter who are missing.
不
No.
Bess
Bess.
Sam
Sam.
你们在干什么
What are you two doing.
Russ Joba
Russ, Joba.
妈 怎么回事
Mom, what is going on.
首先 我不是你老妈
First of all, I'm not your mother.
你别碰她 听到了吗
You leave her alone.You hear me.
你想折磨谁的话 就折磨我吧
If you want to hurt somebody, you hurt me.
真甜蜜啊
That is so sweet.
但是我就是想折磨他
But I am going to hurt her.
和他
And him.
特别是你
But especially you.
因为你把这些猎人引到了这里
For bringing these hunters here.
我要折磨你们所有人
I'm gonna hurt all of you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
Sam 接电话啊 见鬼
Sam, pick up, damn it.
求你了 别这样
Please, don't do this.
别伤害Bess 她是你女儿啊
Not to Bess, she's your daughter.
我到底得强调多少次
How many times do I have to say this.
继女
Step daughter.
我是我们这一族的最后一人
I'm the last of my bloodline.
都是因为你和你那些同族们
Thanks to you and your kind out there.
他醒了
He's awake.
你真是秀色可餐啊
Don't you just look good enough to eat.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this.
我可以理解你想伤害我
I mean, me, I understand.
但是这些人是你的家人啊
But these people are your family.
你的族群
Your pack.
去年冬天
Last winter.
我的弟弟Charlie 被一个猎人杀死了
My little brother Charlie was killed by a hunter.
我的丈夫还劝我要有耐心 要隐忍
My husband counseled patience, restraint.
跟他偷走我们神圣的教堂时一个嘴脸
Just as when he took over our beloved church.
他指引人们走向新的道路
He preached a new direction.
狼人和人类和平共处的道路
Lycanthropes and men would co-exist.
认为和平比统治更重要
Peace was more important than dominance.
我想法设法地帮助他
Tried so hard to make his way work.
努力做一个传教士的妻子
To be a preacher's wife.
但接着 Charlie被杀死了
But then, Charlie was murdered.
于是我不由自主地想到我父亲的布道
And I couldn't help remembering my daddy's sermons.
现在看来他说的才是正确的
And by golly turns out he was right.
只要有人类存在
As long as there's a man.
世界就永无和平之日
There can be no peace.
因为人类只会毁坏
Because man destroys.
而我呢
And I, for one.
我厌倦这一切了
I'm sick of it.
我现在算明白了
I get it now.
既然力量如此强大 为什么还要与人类共存
Why co-exist, when you can rule.
答对了 但是我丈夫并不是这么想的
Bingo, but my husband doesn't see it that way.
他是被咬了才成为狼人 不像我是天生的
See, he's bitten, not born into it, like I was.
他仍然保留有一点人性
He still holds on to his humanity.
这也是为什么我很乐意看到
Which is why I'm so pleased that it will be.
是他挑起了诸神的黄昏 而不是我
His claws that start Ragnarok, not mine.
你跟你哥哥来这里
You and your brother coming here was.
简直就是Fenris的显灵
A blessing from Fenris above.
你们俩把Garth逼得走投无路
The two of you cornered Garth here.
然后当Bess闯进来想看看
And then when Bess came running in to see.
你们到底在搞什么鬼的时候
What the fuss was about.
你残忍的杀害了她
You killed her.
不
No.
她就死在那儿
Here.
银弹穿心
Silver to the heart.
你想拉我做替罪羊
You're gonna frame their murders on me.
我丈夫确实曾对猎人忍气吞声
My husband turned his cheek once.
但这次我不这么认为了
I don't think he can do it again.
离她远点
Hey, get away from her.
杀死你我并不感到快乐
Killing you gives me no joy.
诸神的黄昏
But Ragnarok.
才是重中之重
It's bigger than all of us.
你真变态
You're sick.
你是存心想让我的爪子沾满鲜血吗
You're just dying for me to get my claws dirty, aren't you.
穿着Russ的衣服掩盖掉你的气味
Wearing Russ's coat to hide your scent.
聪明
Smart.
我总是能让人大吃一惊
Well, I'm full of surprises.
我也觉得
As am I.
好好做人 听见了吗
Be good, you hear me.
我会的 谢谢 Sam
I will.Thanks, Sam.
他怎么样了
How's he doing.
他很自责
He's taking it pretty hard.
他觉得自己应该早点儿发现事情不对劲
Feels like he should've seen the signs earlier.
或许你是对的
You know what, maybe you were right.
他看起来是个好人
He seems like a good man.
就这件事而言
Considering.
是啊 你也是对的
Yeah.And you were right.
这里并不是那么完美
Everything around here wasn't copacetic.
我又搞砸了
I screwed up again.
- 先是Kevin 然后这事 - 嘿
- First Kevin, now this. - Hey.
Kevin的事归咎于我
Kevin, that's on me.
是我把他拉进这个圈子里的
I'm the one who pulled him into all this.
我才是那个应该好好保护他的人
I'm the one who should've been there to protect him.
我们都要为自己的错误
Well, guess there's enough of that blame.
承担责任嘛
To go around then.
- Dean - 嗯
- Dean - Yeah.
我知道这听起来有点疯狂 但是
I know this may sound a little crazy, but.
或许我可以回去然后跟你一起猎魔
Maybe I could come back and hunt with you.
有我狼人的力量 我们是有优势的
I mean, with my werewolf mojo, we'd have an advantage.
听着 Garth
Look, Garth.
Dean 我想要弥补这一切
Dean, I want to make this right.
我本不应该离开你们的 尤其是Kevin
I never should've left you guys, especially Kevin.
Kevin是我的朋友
Kevin was my friend.
而朋友间是不会这么做的
Friends don't do that.
你说得对
Well, hey, you said it.
谁在乎幸福是从何而来的
You know, who cares where happiness comes from.
我们都有点奇怪 有点神经质
Look, we're all little weird, we're all little wacky.
比其他人怪得多
Some more than others.
但是如果那样行得通 就那样吧
But if it works, it works.
你这里还有事
You get something here.
即使他们是狼人
Okay?Even though they are werewolves.
还是狼化人什么的
Lycanthropes, whatever.
不要放手 懂吗
Don't let that go, okay.
否则你永远都不会原谅自己的
Or you'll never forgive yourself.
而且 你还得快快乐乐地
Besides somebody's got to live to.
生活下去 不能让这件事情就这么石沉大海
Tell this damn story someday and who better than you.
赶紧闭嘴 过来给我抱一个
Now shut up and come here.
- 真的吗 - 快点 在我改变主意之前
- Really? - Hurry up, before I change my mind.
- 我会寄明信片给你的 - 好
- I'll send you that postcard. - Yeah.
喂
Hey.
听着 那天晚上
Listen, that night that, uh.
就是咱们决定分头行动那天
That we went our separate ways.
你是说我们分道扬镳那天吗
You mean that you and I split.
这样说也没错
Fair enough.
那时我状态很不好
I was messed-up, man.
Kevin死了 而我
Kevin was dead, and I.
我也不知道我是怎么了
I don't know what I was.
好
Okay.
好吧 我现在也还没缓过来
Hell, maybe I still don't.
但 我也知道我对你态度不是特别好
But, um, I know I took a piece of you in the process.
关于这一点
And for that.
就好像有人改变了剧本 懂吗
Somebody changed the playbook, you know.
好像对的事情其实是错的
It's like what's right is wrong, and.
错的事情更错
What's wrong is more wrong, and.
我知道当
I just know that when.
当我们一起行动的时候
When we rode together.
情况只会更糟
We split the crappiness.
是啊 所以
Yeah, so.
好吧
Okay.
好
Dean 我们之间已经出现问题了
But something is broken here, Dean.
我没说没有问题
I'm not saying is not, I.
我就是觉得如果有时间我们可以一起喝一杯
Maybe we need to put a couple W's on the board.
说不定就能和好如初什么的
And we get past all this.
我不认为这样
I don't think so.
不 我希望是这样
No, I wish.
我们对事情的看法不再一样
We don't see things in the same way anymore.
我们看待事物的角度也不一样了
Our roles in this whole thing.
那次在教堂里
Back in that church.
说服我把地狱封起来
Talking me out of boarding up hell.
或是耍伎俩让Gadreel附我的身
Or tricking me into letting Gadreel possess me.
我没法再相信你了
I can't trust you.
不能像以前那样给予你信任
Not the way I thought I could.
不能像我应该做的那样无话不谈
Not the way I should be able to.
好吧 不管发生什么事
Okay, well, whatever happened.
我们是一家人 好吗
We're family, okay.
你说得好像这句话是万灵药一样
You say that like it's some sort of cure-all.
好像它能够改变事实
Like it can change the fact.
我们之间会变成这样
That everything, that have ever gone wrong between us.
都是因为我们是一家人
Has been because we're family.
那我们 不再是一家人了吗
So what, we're not family now.
我是说 如果你想要一起工作的话
I'm saying, you wanna work.
那就一起工作
Let's work.
但如果你想要成为兄弟的话
If you want to be brothers.
该说的我都说了
Those're my terms.